漫威影业出品
愿你的邻居尊重你
May your neighbors respect you...
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
灾难远离你
trouble neglect you...
■
翻译：夜魔Joy  夜魔开
天使庇护你
the angels protect you...
翻译：铁链斯嘉丽  夜魔奶
天堂收留你
and heaven accept you.
校对：夜魔奶
敬美好的生活
To better days.
-干杯  -干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
时间轴：腋毛二苏
是谁
Hey, who is that guy?
-别紧张  伙计们  -住手
- Easy, lads. - Whoa, whoa, whoa.
后期：聪炒吉丁  8T     总监：夜魔奶
费恩
Finn.
我得到消息后赶了最早的航班
Caught the first flight soon as I heard.
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
情况有些糟糕
Terrible circumstances.
但能见到你  我很高兴
But it sure is good to see you.
好兄弟
Be a good lad.
去给我们的朋友费恩倒杯酒
Go fetch our friend Finn a drink.
你叫罗里
It's Rory...
对吗
isn't it?
这里面是他吧
This is him, then?
我不想让他步我的后尘...
I didn't want him to follow my footsteps...
但他却一意孤行
but he insisted.
他想闯出一番名堂  可是结果呢
He came over to make his fortune and now, look.
一文不名地死去
Two cents to his name.
他是个好孩子  费恩
He was a good kid, Finn.
然而已经死了
And now he's dead.
也许你离开这行太久  所以不记得了
You know, maybe you've been out of the game too long to remember.
死亡...是这种生活的一部分
Death... is part of the deal.
别插手  别插手
Leave it, leave it.
天哪
Holy shit.
老天爷...
Jesus...
谢谢
Cheers.
你们没什么异议吧
Yous all all right, yeah?
-没有  -真的吗
- Oh, yeah. - Yeah?
是的
Yeah.
这个该死的枪手
Now, this bloody shooter,
偷了我一百二十万
he stole $1.2 million of my money.
杀了我的孩子  我失了一个手下
Man takes my son. I lose a boy.
还拿走我的钱
He takes my money.
我一定要让他血债血偿
I'm getting it back.
拷问这城里的每一个人
We will beat every mother's son in this city
拿回我的钱
till I have my money in my hands,
留这个枪手一条命  跪在我面前谢罪
and this shooter's on his knees, alive.
不然你们会有更多人进棺材
Or there'll be more of you shining the inside of a box!
都听懂了吗
Do you hear me?
出去
Get out!
出去  都出去
Get out! Move! Let's go!
那个杀了我们兄弟的枪手
That bastard shooter that massacred our brothers.
-他在哪  -我不知道
- Where is he? - I don't know!
是新面孔
New faces.
接受过军事训练
Military training.
-快点想  -我不知道  别  别
- Think fast! - I don't know! Wait, wait!
等一下  我可能见过这样一个人
Wait! I might have seen one guy!
抱歉打扰了  说你呢  你好吗
Hey, excuse me! Yeah, you. How's it going, huh?
-天哪  -今天过得好吗
- Oh, Jesus. - You having a good day?
我们在找一个人
We're looking for a customer.
-什么  -穿着夹克...
- What? - Wears a jacket...
据说在大夏天里也穿着
even in the middle of summer, or so they say.
我...我...
I... I mean...
你还有两个脚踝  两个膝盖  一个手肘
Now, I count two ankles, two knees, one elbow.
你猜怎么着  我正好还有五发子弹
And guess what? I got five more rounds.
我不...
I don't...
我想起来了  他有条狗  对吗
I think I know. Has a dog, right?
他来过这  我还见过他带狗散步
Came in here. I even saw him walk it once.
给我仔细说清楚
Elaborate.
坐下
Sit.
搜一下柜子里
Search the closets.
这是我们的狗  就是这里
Dog's one of ours. This is the place.
-柜子是空的  -找到我的钱
- Nah, it's empty. - Find my goddamn money.
你们都听到了  行动
You heard him. Let's go!
他不喜欢住豪宅吧
He's not one for fancy living, is he?
把那个拉出来
Pull that up.
让狗闭嘴
Shut that damn dog up!
别叫了
Hey! Knock it off!
没有  这没有钱
Uh, nothing... but it ain't money.
钱不在这
The money's not here.
这就是你的真面目
That's who you are.
快走
Move it.
夜
魔
侠
第二季  第四集
-我马上就好  -好的
- I'm just about ready. - Okay.
-我帮你  -谢谢
- Uh, here, let me help with that. - Oh, thanks.
没关系
It's okay.
抱歉
Sorry.
-你还好吧  -还好
- You okay? - Yeah.
我只是...
I'm just, uh...
在恢复中
recovering.
从什么当中恢复
From what?
我也说不上来
I don't really know the name for it.
但是...你感觉好多了吧
But... you're feeling better?
是的
Yeah.
现在
Now.
跟你一起
With you.
虽然我看不到  但你似乎很会打领带
Not that I can verify, but you seem good at this.
因为我哥哥不怎么会  所以我就学会了
Uh, well, my brother wasn't, so that's where I came in.
你从没说过你有个哥哥
You never said you had a brother.
你也没问过
Uh... you never asked.
谢谢
Uh, thank you.
走吧  快到时间了
Come on. It's about time.
"在耶和华眼中
"Precious in the eyes of the Lord...
看圣民之死  极为宝贵"[《圣经》旧约]
is the death of his saints."
但是...
Well...
艾略特·格罗托并不是圣民
Elliot Grote was no saint.
他只是一个人
He was human...
有很多缺点
deeply flawed.
我记得  每个星期日
Every Sunday, for as far as I remember...
艾略特会过来
Elliot would come here...
孤身一人  没有朋友
friendless and alone...
来坐坐
to sit.
就在那张长凳上
right there in that pew.
我经常会看到他
Often, I would see him take...
不管有多少钱
whatever money he had...
揉在一起的几百块  一点零钱
crumpled one hundreds, loose change...
甚至有一次是一块劳力士
a Rolex watch one time...
都会放在募捐板上
and put it in the collection plate...
希望得到救赎
hoping for redemption.
永远遥不可及的救赎
Which would never come.
希望得到光明...
Praying for the light...
但艾略特到死都身处黑暗之中
but Elliot died still in the dark...
没有人为他哀悼...
with no one to mourn his loss...
除了你们三个
except the three of you.
所以  我们也许能说...
And so, we might say...
一条生命逝去了...
one life gone...
那是一条罪恶的生命...
one sinful life...
但是他不仅仅是一个人
but one person is not just one person.
我们每个人心中都有一个世界
In each of us, there is a world...
与人交际  接触他人
webbing out, reaching others.
创造反应
Creating reactions.
有并驾齐驱之时...
Sometimes equal...
亦有针锋相对之时
sometimes opposite.
我们经常说  一条生命逝去了
We rush to say, one life gone...
但每个人都有一个世界
but each of us is a world.
而今天
And today,
一个世界消逝了
a world has been lost.
我们不是很了解他  但我...
We didn't know him well, but I...
从来不觉得一个人应该孤独地死去
never loved the idea of letting anyone die alone.
他...他不是一个人吗
He... he wasn't alone?
他们发现他和地狱狂狗的人死在一起吧
They found him surrounded by knocked out Dogs of Hell, right?
这些天来我都分不清这些坏人了
I get all the bad guys confused these days.
我还以为现在
Didn't think it could get
暴力情况已经够糟了  但是...
much worse out there, the violence, but...
我等下回办公室找你们吧
What if I meet you back at the office?
我想再在这里待一会
I'm just gonna take a minute here.
行啊
Yeah, sure.
-布道很棒  -谢谢
- It was a nice sermon. - Thank you.
很多牧师会喜欢
Most priests would have found
多说说逝者的好事  但...
something kind to say about the man himself, but...
我说他会来教堂
I said he came to church.
人们都会说死者的好话  马修
Nothing shines up a halo faster than a death, Matthew.
但是葬礼是给生者看的
But funerals are for the living...
篡改过去...
and revising history...
只会冲淡我们应该吸取的教训
only dilutes the lessons we should learn from it.
那不是我的错
It wasn't my fault.
-你说什么  -格罗托的死
- What wasn't? - Grotto's death.
-没有人说是你的错  -是啊
- No one said it was. - Yeah.
城里新来了一个家伙  他...
There's a new man in town, he's, uh...
杀人根本不眨眼
killing people in cold blood.
我听说爱尔兰人出的事了
Yeah, I read about what happened with the Irish.
这几晚...你肯定很忙
Must have been a... busy couple nights.
是啊  我尽了全力
Yeah, I did everything I could to...
保护我的委托人
uh, protect my client.
-这个工作已经结束了  马修  -因为我失败了
- That work is done, Matthew. - Because I failed.
至少你努力过了
At least you tried.
正如你所说  他的生命也有价值
Well, like you said, his life had value.
一个世界逝去了
A whole world's been lost
其他人也在一个接一个地死去
and others are dying one after the other--
马修  你想寻求什么
Matthew, what are you looking for?
-宽恕  -宽恕什么
- Forgiveness. - For what?
没有做到更多
Uh... not doing more?
你刚刚说你已经尽了全力
You just said you did everything you could.
如果你还是我认识的你  我相信你说的是实话
If you're the man I understand you to be, I'm sure that's true.
那我为什么仍有罪恶感
Then why do I still feel guilty?
有罪恶感也许是一件好事
Guilt can be a good thing.
是你的灵魂感召你去行动
It's the soul's call to action.
说明...
The indication that...
有些事情不对劲
something is wrong.
唯一让你...
The only way...
释怀的办法...
to rid your heart of it...
就是纠正你的错误  继续前行
is to correct your mistakes and keep going...
直到弥补你的过错
until amends are made.
我不知道你有什么未做到之事或该做之事
I don't know what you didn't do or what you should have done...
但罪恶感
but the guilt...
罪孽
the guilt...
说明你还没有完成你的使命
means your work is not yet finished.
谢谢
Thank you.
他还有气已经够走运了
He's lucky to be alive.
这是地检为她的案子收集的证据
This is all of the stuff that the DA's collecting for her case.
大多数是关于惩罚者的受害者
And most of it's about the Punisher's victims.
地狱狂犬  毒贩团伙
The Dogs of Hell, the cartel...
但其中还有这个
But this was in the middle of it.
不是被他击中的人  而是他
Not someone he shot, him.
他疯了  也许他朝自己开枪了
He's insane. Maybe he shot himself.
我也想过  但是距离这么近
I thought about that, but at that close of a range...
是  他早就死定了
Yeah, he'd be dead already.
我不是疑神疑鬼
Okay, not to go all tin-foil hat here,
但是陶瓦塞给我这些档案肯定是有原因的
but Tower obviously slipped this to me for a reason.
万一惩罚者并不是最可怕的呢
What if the Punisher isn't the worst of it?
万一雷耶斯试图掩盖些什么
What if Reyes is trying to cover something up?
你觉得那个大开杀戒的疯子还不算最可怕的
You think that murderous psychopath isn't the worst of it?
是的  我觉得唯一能保护尼尔森-默多克律所的办法
No. And I think our best shot at protecting Nelson and Murdock
就是找到他
is to find him.
这是我们唯一自毁前途的办法
It's our best shot at career suicide...
还是自讨子弹吃
or just getting shot.
-我疯了吗  -尼尔森-默多克律所
- Am I insane? - Nelson and Murdock.
-马特  -你说什么
- Matt? - Sorry, what?
没什么...
Nothing, just...
我想应该是兰顿牧师的悼词对我影响太大了
Father Lantom's eulogy really got to me, I guess.
是啊  他确实很有一套
Yeah, he does that.
惩罚者是个疯子
Mmm, Punisher's a lunatic.
但你仍然很在意吗
But you care, anyway?
那倒不是  更像是
I wouldn't say that, it's more like...
好奇
curious.
这些文件  雷耶斯的痴迷
In between these files and... and Reyes' obsession
再加上人类是一种
and the fact that humans are
很复杂的物种这个事实前提
a pretty complicated species to begin with,
我就
I just...
我就觉得肯定还有别的故事
I feel like there's gotta be more to the story.
我觉得你...
I think you are...
不会吧  你觉得我疯了
Oh, my God, you think I'm insane.
我开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
富有同情心
Compassionate.
这是一种美德  凯伦
It's a good quality, Karen.
圣人的品质
Stuff of saints.
我可不是什么圣人
Yeah, well, I'm no saint.
你简直不知道这让我有多高兴
I can't tell you how glad I am to hear that.
马特
Matt!
有活生生的非罪犯客户需要我们的帮助
We have real, live, non-criminal clients who need our help.
-失陪一下  -好
- Excuse me for a second. - Yeah.
说说看
Tell me.
迪佩什塔先生把楼里的电梯弄坏了
Mr. DiPesta defaced the elevator in his building.
严格来说  他就是罪犯了
Which, technically, makes him a criminal.
他的包租公  抱歉
That's what his slumlord, excuse me,
房东是这么说的  但你看
landlord says, but look.
他一没空调  二没热水
He's got no AC, no hot water.
这简直就是尼尔森-默多克律所的菜啊
This has Nelson and Murdock written all over it.
但我们今天就要立案
But we gotta file today.
凯伦
Karen!
-也许她临时出去了  -她把文件带走了吗
- Maybe she stepped out. - Did she take the files?
-什么  -雷耶斯的文件
- Huh? - From Reyes.
惩罚者的文件
The... the Punisher files.
该死
Oh, shit.
我得去找她
I have to find her.
先找他
Find him first.
你来早了
You're early.
你知道我不喜欢被人催
You know I don't like being rushed.
-我需要那套衣服  梅尔文  -我猜到了
- I need the suit, Melvin. - Yeah, I figured.
你知道吗  你的突发奇想
You know, you getting popped in the noggin
让我尝试
gave me a chance to try
某种新的玩意儿  我可激动了
some new stuff and I'm pretty excited about it.
强化的  碳管头盔
Fortified, carbon tube helmet.
这都快刀枪不入了
I mean, it's pretty damn close to indestructible.
-有多坚固  -你自己来测试吧
- How close? - I'll leave the testing to you.
我额外送你几个强化合金手套
I threw in some reinforced alloy gloves.
谁知道呢  小心点好
You know, what the hell. Gotta be careful.
某些新人在外面杀了不少人
Some new people spilling a lot of blood out there.
谁
Who?
不知道
Don't know.
但我所有的老主顾
But all my old contacts are
又来请我给他们提供装备
showing up again begging me to outfit 'em.
你答应了吗
Did you?
没  我不再干了  我把他们都回绝了
No, I don't do that anymore. I turned them all away.
-你看起来好多了  -对啊  感觉好多了
- Oh, you look better. - Yeah, I feel better.
你康复了  我挺高兴的
Glad you're on the mend.
我也是
So am I.
好了  在外面注意安全  好吗
Well, stay safe out there, will you?
谢谢  梅尔文  你也是
Thanks, Melvin. You too.
我可不会冒险  看看这个
Oh, I'm not taking any chances. Check this out.
要为了贝兹坚强起来
Gotta stay strong for Betsy.
你想看看吗  这可厉害了
You wanna take a look? I mean, it's pretty wicked.
我相信你
I'm gonna take your word for it.
乔治·巴克
Uh, George Buck?
你好  医院说我也许能在这儿找到你
Hi, the hospital told me I might find you here.
你好  你是跟他们一伙的吗
Hi, uh... are you one of them?
抱歉  跟谁一伙
Sorry, one of who?
求你了  别找我麻烦
Please, just leave me alone.
我不会对你做任何事的
I'm not gonna do anything to you.
如果有  也是想帮你找回工作
If anything, I'd like to help you get your job back.
听着  我需要知道为什么你
Look, I need to understand why you were
当初被市综合医院开除了
fired from Metro-General in the first place.
我能请你喝杯咖啡吗
Could I buy you a cup of coffee?
拍这张照片的时候你跟他在一起吗
You were with him when this was taken?
对  那枪打穿了他的脑袋
Yeah. That bullet tore through his head.
没几个人能挺过来
Not many people survive that.
好吧  我想知道你能记起什么
Well, I'd like to know what you remember.
无名氏
John Doe.
他是彻头彻尾的植物人
Guy was a total vegetable.
所以我想他们才决定一个护士就够了
I guess that's why they decided he only needed one nurse.
有家人或者探病的人吗
Any family or visitors?
没有
No.
我是说
I mean...
除了那些穿西装的
aside from the suits.
-西装  -对
- Suits? - Yeah.
有时候是一帮男的  有时候是一帮女的
Uh, sometimes men, sometimes women.
很明显  因为他们都戴着一样的耳机
You can tell 'em 'cause they all wear the same ear pieces.
那个和黑西装
That and the... black suits.
就有点像
Kind of like... uh...
知道这些西装人士是谁吗
Got any idea who these suits were?
不清楚
No.
但他们是管事的
Uh, but they had their run of the place
是他们催人家DNR的
and they were the ones that pushed for the, uh, the DNR.
-不施行心肺复苏吗  -对
- A "Do not resuscitate"? - Yeah.
他们办好了文件
They had the paperwork.
医生拔掉插管的时候我就在那儿
And I was there when the doctor pulled the plug.
我  我有点糊涂
I... I'm confused.
你说这个人死了吗
You're saying this guy died?
对  死了大概一分钟
Yeah, for about a minute.
是挺疯狂的  但他们说有时候会这样
It's crazy, but they say it happens sometimes.
前一分钟刚死  然后突然之间
You know, one minute, flatline, then boom.
他的心脏又重新跳动了
His heart starts back up again.
自己动的
On its own.
他不甘心就这么死了
He just didn't wanna die.
他醒来后不到十分钟
Within ten minutes of being awake...
就伸手抓着我的手术衣
he reaches up and grabs my scrubs,
拽着让我俯下身  离得很近  说
yanks me down, and says, real close...
"带我回家"
"Take me home."
我不该那么做
I shouldn't have done it.
我早该知道会害我被开除的
I should've known it'd get me fired.
他家
His home.
你有地址吗
Do you have an address?
今晚真不错
Nice night.
我不是一个人
I'm not alone.
你想跟我们一起来吗
You wanna come with us?
还是想弄个一团糟
Or you wanna make a mess?
别开枪
Don't shoot!
抓活的
We want him alive!
谁想抓活的
Who, who needs me alive?
-放下  放下  -放下
- Drop it! Drop it! - Drop it!
冷静  大家冷静  都不许开枪
Calm down! Everyone, calm down! No one shoot!
谢谢你干掉了几个人
Well, thanks for thinning out the herd.
你被包围了  孩子
You're surrounded, son.
当个乖孩子  把枪放下
Now be a good lad and drop the iron.
快点
Come on.
你似乎挺聪明的
You seem like a smart one.
-告诉卡特  我们这儿快弄完了  -明白
- Tell Carter we're about done here. - Got it.
我们这就调查完斯坦利酒吧谋杀现场  完毕
We're finishing up the murder scene at Stanley's Bar. Over.
收到
Copy.
我得知道这儿发生了什么
I need to know what happened here.
我什么也不会说的
I'm not telling you shit.
你帮我们抓住了菲斯克
You helped us catch Fisk,
并不代表我们就变成朋友了
that don't make us friends.
是惩罚者干的吗
Was this the Punisher?
天啊
Jesus.
爱尔兰人  明白吗
The Irish, okay?
为了找到惩罚者  他们悬赏他的脑袋
To find the Punisher. They put a bounty on his head.
现在全地狱厨房的人都可能受伤
Now people all over the Kitchen are getting hurt.
外面简直像蛮荒的西部一样
It's the goddamn Wild West out there.
爱尔兰人找到他了吗
Have the Irish found him?
我们还能接到这样的电话  大概是没找到
As long as we keep getting calls like this, I guess not.
别插手  听见没
Hey, stay out of it. You hear me?
我只是想帮忙  警官
I just wanna help, Sergeant.
不  你帮不上忙
No, you can't help.
你才是问题所在
You're the problem!
因为你  警察形同虚设
'Cause of you, the uniform means dick.
警察不再防止犯罪  而是被它牵着跑
Cops are no longer preventing crime, we're just chasing it.
帮你们这种人收拾烂摊子
Mopping up the mess that you people leave in your wake.
你我站在同一边
We're on the same side, you and I.
你只站在你自己那边
You're on your own side.
2A  有开火  65街横向  旋转木马旁
2-Adam, shots fired. 65th Street transverse, by the carousel.
全体回归
All units to back.
15分局收到  总调度部
Fifteen Sergeant responding, Central.
卡塞尔
谁干的
Who did this?
一个你惹不起的人
People you don't mess with.
你在流血  而我有一整晚陪你耗
You're bleeding out. And I got all night.
去死吧
Go to hell!
谁干的
Who did it?
他们叫他惩罚者
The one they call Punisher.
他在哪
Where is he?
那无关紧要  因为我们收拾完后
It doesn't matter 'cause when we're done with him,
他就死定了
he's as good as dead.
这话很有帮助啊
That's helpful.
但我问的不是这个
But it's not what I asked.
你一把AK使得真是如火纯青啊
You're quite an artist with the AK, aren't ya?
内斯比特
Nesbitt.
凯利
Kelly...
我的长子
my oldest boy.
他们都因为你而上天堂
Every one gone to the angels because of you.
你活不过今晚
You're dying tonight.
坑已经挖好了
The hole's been dug.
但我给你个机会
But I'm giving you one chance to meet your maker
让你四肢健全地见上帝
with arms and legs attached.
宽容是我的特质
Generosity's my defining trait.
你想吃点东西吗
You care for a nibble?
不想吗
No?
随便你了
Ah, suit yourself.
能让我镇静下来
Helps calm me nerves.
你觉得我紧张
I look nervous to you?
小子们
Boys.
让我们单独待一会儿
Give us a moment.
我要拿回我的钱
I want my money back.
你的儿子死了  你却想要钱
Your kid's in a box, but you want your money. Huh?
复仇可能不是爱尔兰人发明的
The Irish may not have invented revenge,
但我们确实花了时间去改进它
but we sure as hell took some time perfecting it.
别以为我没见过你这种行为
Don't think you're showing me something I haven't seen before,
因为你大肆杀戮
'cause your killing spree
符合寻仇者的所有特征
has all the signs of a man seeking retribution.
我说得对吗
Am I right?
好吧
Okay.
我告诉你
I'll tell you...
我告诉你钱在哪
I'll tell you where your money is.
我向你保证  马上就会结束
I promise you, it'll be over soon.
马上就好
In a jiffy.
快说吧
Come on, yeah?
感觉如何
How'd that feel?
小子们  按住他
Boys, hold him down!
来吧  来吧
Come on! Come on!
我就希望是这样
Oh, I was hoping it would come to this.
是吗
Yeah?
你是真要做  还是随便说说而已
You gonna do it or you gonna talk about it?
我就在这
I'm here!
我要把你们这帮混蛋全杀了
I'll kill every one of you bastards!
来吧  我要杀了你
Come on, I'll kill you!
你想让我钻哪儿  这里吗
Where would you like it? Here, huh? Here?
现在怎么不逞英雄了
Not such a big man now, are ya?
《一炉饼干  两炉饼干》
一路饼干  两路饼干  你给我一角  我给你一分
那是什么
What was that?
默夫
Murph?
-去那边  -好
- Take that side. - All right.
-注意着点  -好
- Keep eyes on. - All right.
好了
All right.
新法子
New plan.
带进来
Bring him in.
好像你挺喜欢这只杂种狗的
It seems like you've taken a liking to this mutt.
乖  乖  听话
Good boy, good boy. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
如果我拿不到我的钱
Hey, if I don't get my money...
我对你做的所有事
everything I've done to you,
我都会加倍用在这只狗身上
I'm doing double to poor Fido here, huh?
听话  听话
Good boy, good boy, huh.
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait.
放它走  放它走  你个混蛋
Hey, let him go, just let him go, you asshole.
我跟你说你的钱在哪  我说
I'll tell you where your money is, okay? I'll tell you.
你的钱在一辆货车里放着  在一辆货车里
Your money's in a van, okay? It's in a van.
停在第48街和第10大道交叉口
It's on 48th and 10th.
放它
Just let him...
放它走  混蛋  放它走
Just let him go, you asshole, let him go.
他是爱动物人士  真有爱
He's an animal lover. That's sweet.
把它带出去
Take him out.
走了  走
Come on, let's go.
如果你不介意的话
Now, if you don't mind...
在钱到手之前我先留着你这条命
I'll keep you alive until the cash is safe at hand.
好吗
Yeah?
第48街和第10大道
48th and 10th.
对  动作要快
Yeah, make it quick.
小心点
And watch your backside.
抓住他
Get him.
对  我觉得很顺利
Yeah, I think it went well.
-是  还是老一套  -我知道
- Yeah, it's the same old story. - I know, I know. I hear ya.
-你还能怎么办  -对  没办法
- What are you gonna do about it, right? - Ah, nothing.
对
Yeah.
对  我找到箱子了
Yeah, I got the case.
等一下
Hold on.
对  钱都在  费恩先生
Yeah, the money's all here, Mr. Finn.
等等  有别的东西
Wait, wait, there's something else.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
他挣脱了  过来
He's loose. Get down here.
吉米  肖恩
Jimmy! Shaun!
吉米
Jimmy!
吉米  肖恩
Jimmy! Shaun!
这就是你想要的
You wanted this.
不  我就指望着这一刻了
No, I counted on it.
现在我能面对面问你话了
Now I can ask you face to face.
那天谁在那儿  谁杀了我全家
Who was there that day? Who killed my family?
-你全家  -对
- Your family? - Yeah.
-谁在乎啊  -快
- Who cares? - Move!
快  快
Move! Go, go, go!
打死那个狗娘养的
Shoot that son of a bitch!
我们抓住他了  快来
We got him! Come on! Yeah!
-快过来  -一炉饼干  两炉饼干
- Get down here! - One batch, two batch.
一分换一角
Penny and dime.
他们要付出代价的  妈的每个人都别想逃
They're gonna pay. Every single goddamn one of 'em.
他们会的
They will.
但不是今晚  走吧
But not tonight. Move.
那儿  那个屋子
There! That room there.
-不要杀人  -小侍童
- No killing. - Altar boy.
好了  咱们离开这儿
All right, let's get out of here.
来
Come on.
不赖啊你
Not bad.
谢了
Thanks.
我想是我
I guess I, uh...
我想是我错了
I guess I was wrong.
什么
About?
说你是个怂蛋
About you being a pussy.
现在别给我花言巧语的  弗兰克
Don't get all sweet on me now, Frank.
-马上就有人来帮忙了  -不用
- Help's on the way. - Nah.
你该走了
You should go.
我没救了
I'm past saving.
起码我还有人作伴  对吧
At least I'd have company, right?
我想我可能要死了
I think I might cash out.
你本来可以当个厉害的海军陆战队员  小红
You'd have made a hell of a Marine, Red.
那句词
That rhyme.
-什么意思  -你说什么
- What's it mean? - What'd you say?
你说的那个
Thing you say.
就在你开枪之前
Right before you pull the trigger.
你什么
What do you...
你听到了
You heard that?
对  我听到了
Yeah, I heard it.
活见鬼了
What the...
我得说啊  有时候
I gotta say, sometimes...
有时候我觉得你也许真是恶魔
Sometimes I think you really just might be the devil.
有时候我也那样觉得
Sometimes I think I might be, too.
那是
It's, uh...
一炉饼干  两炉饼干
One batch, two batch.
一分换一角
Penny and dime, you know.
那是她最喜欢的书
It was her favorite book.
知道吗  你
You know, you...
你得漂洋过海  冲锋陷阵
You gotta cross the ocean... and go fight.
你懂的
You see...
一直以来你以为你会很害怕
whole time you're thinking you're gonna be scared, right?
然而  你却没有
But then, you're not.
那对我来说其实一直很简单
See, that part of it was always easy for me.
杀戮
Killing.
即使看着我的同伴死去  那都...
Even watching my buddies die, it just...
那都没什么意义
it didn't mean nothing.
我第一次感到害怕
The first time I got scared...
是在回家的飞机上
was on a plane on the way home.
我一直以为上帝
I kept thinking God was
已经要抛弃我们了
gonna pull the rug out from under us, you know?
该死  那就是他的幽默
Shit, that's his kind of funny, you know.
但是飞机平安到达  我们都回到了家
But the plane landed safe and we were home.
随着车流
Driving through traffic.
你经过那些快餐店  甜甜圈店  和那些
Yeah, you pass fast food and donut shops and all that...
油腻的垃圾
that greasy shit.
都是你努力战斗所保护的东西  然后车停了
It's the shit you fought to protect and then the car stops.
我们在她的学校外
We were outside her school.
我就去了她的班级
I get to her classroom, right?
她就在那儿
She's in there...
但她不知道
but she's got no idea.
她不知道爸爸回家了
She's got no idea that Daddy's home.
我走进去  那些孩子根本没在学习  他们...
I walk in, these kids, they're not even studying, they're...
在做什么瑜伽
doing some kind of yoga. Yeah.
你知道吗
You know?
她就在那儿
She's there.
她在摆她的姿势
She's doing her poses, you know.
她在下腰  她在扭动
She's bending and, you know, she's moving.
她看上去就像一朵鲜花
She looks like a flower.
没错
Yeah.
你根本没法理解
And, you know, you can't even understand it,
怎么会有这种...
you know, how does something like that have...
怎么会有如此美丽...
How does something that beautiful...
怎么会...
How does that...
是我的孩子呢
does that come from me, you know?
她抬起头来  看到了我
And she looks up and she sees me.
我看到了她
I see her.
天啊  那是真的
By God, that's real.
是真的  小红
That's real, Red.
突然  她从教室那一头冲过来
In an instant, she's across that classroom floor,
扑到了我的怀里
she's in my arms.
她把我抱得这么紧
She's squeezing me so tight,
我敢说我的肋骨都快断了
I swear I was gonna bust a rib, you know?
我们就这样站在那里  拥抱着彼此
We just stayed there like that, we're holding each other.
老师用手机把这一幕都拍了下来
Teacher, she's filming the whole thing on her phone, you know,
她准备放到网上一类的
she's gonna put it on YouTube or some shit.
她拿不稳  因为她...
She can't hold the thing steady, because, you know, she's...
她哭得太凶了  小孩们都在哭
she's bawling so hard, and the kids are all wailing,
他们在尖声大叫  我呢
you know, they're screaming. And me?
该死  我哭得最凶  我...
Shit, I'm the worst of all. I'm a...
我这种扑克脸的家伙
I'm a rubber-face clown, you know.
我哭得特别凶
I cried so hard.
但我的孩子却没哭
But not my baby.
我的宝贝没哭
Not my girl.
她是我的宝贝  她...
You know, she's my girl. She's...
她没哭  她抱着我
She's not crying, she's holding me up.
我的宝贝  她就这样支撑着我
My girl, she's keeping me on my feet.
她说  我知道  爸爸  我知道
She says, "I knew it, Daddy. I knew it."
然后我们回家了  我的妻子  儿子
And then we go home. Wife, the boy.
家还是原来的样子
Place is the exact same.
感觉好像他们
It's like it was just holding
屏住了呼吸等我回来一样
its breath waiting for me to get back, you know?
然后我突然意识到
Then it hit me.
一切痛苦
All of it, you know.
我第一次感觉到我有多累  我只是...
The first time I felt how tired I was, you know, I was just...
累了
tired, you know?
你...
You...
你有没有累过  小红
You ever been tired, Red?
有
Yeah.
所以你知道
So, you know.
但是  我却无能为力
It's just, I couldn't do nothing, you know?
所有的一切
All the things...
我没法陪我妻子入睡
I couldn't take my wife to bed.
和我儿子踢球  该死...
Ball with the boy. Shit...
我太累了  我甚至都喝不下一杯啤酒
I was too tired, I couldn't even drink a goddamn beer, you know.
但她却没有
But not her.
我的女儿很开心
My girl was up.
她想让我
See, she wanted me to, uh...
她想让我给她盖好被子  她...
she wanted me to tuck her in. She...
她早就长大了  她知道  但她不在乎
She outgrew it, she knew it, but she didn't care.
她就是想
She wanted it.
她有一本书
She had that book.
她最喜欢的书就在枕头边上
Her favorite book was out on the pillows.
一炉饼干  两炉饼干
One Batch, Two Batch...
你给我一角我给你一分
Penny and Dime.
我以前每天晚上都给她念这本书
I read her that book every night before this shit.
我每一天都会念  但是现在不用念了
I read it every single night, but, see, that was over now
因为爸爸回家了
because Daddy's home now.
她看着我  她求我  小红
She looked at me and she begged me, Red.
她求我
She begged.
我说  不行
I said, "No.
爸爸太累了
Daddy's too tired, see.
但我...
But I'll...
我明天晚上给你念
I'll read to you tomorrow night.
我明天晚上给你念  我保证
I'll read to you tomorrow night, I promise." Yeah.
没想到
Never think that...
对她来说再也没有明天了
for her there was not gonna be any tomorrow, see.
最后一次看到她时
The last time I'd see her,
我将她失去生气的躯壳抱在怀里
I'd be holding her lifeless body in my arms.
肉块从她身上滚落  小红
Meat was spilling out of her, Red.
她已经面目全非
The place where her face used to be.
我觉得我完了  小红
I think I'm done... Red.
我想我完了
I think I'm done.
警察  不许动
Police. Don't move.
把手放在我看得见的地方
Hands where I can see 'em.
枪战
Shots fired.
尸体  一团乱
Bodies, mayhem and shit.
我一猜就是你
How come I just knew it had to be you?
我有东西给你  警官
I have something for you, Sergeant.
是他吗
That's him?
-叫救护车  -是
- Cover him and get EMS. - Yep.
至于你  你这个麻烦精
And you, you incredible pain in my ass.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
帮帮他
Get him help.
闭嘴
Shut up.
-当成是你抓到的  -什么
- Take the collar. - What?
你听到了
You heard me.
是你抓到他的  不是我
You caught him, not me.
不能是我  必须是你
It can't be me, it has to be you.
为什么
Why?
为了保护地狱厨房
To protect the Kitchen.
为了法律和秩序
For law, for order.
你现在是在教我写报告吗
You're telling me how to file a report now?
是的  就是你抓到的
Yeah. Take the collar.
把功劳揽过来  如果可以利用它升个职
Take the credit. Get a promotion, if you can.
-这是你应得的  -放屁
- You've earned it. - Bullshit.
不  需要告诉人们最终是司法体系战胜了一切
No, people have to know the system works.
而不是他的或者我的正义感
Not his justice and not mine.
义警维持秩序的日子结束了  现在由警察负责
Vigilante days are done in this town. The police are in charge.
可是并不是那么回事
That's not how it happened.
那就让它看起来是这么回事
Then make it how it happened.
妈的
Shit.
救护车及支援已在路上  两分钟后到
EMT and backup on the way. Two minutes out.
走
Go.
快走
Go!
我不知道你是什么人...
I don't know what you are...
但我知道你跟他不同
but I know you ain't him.
弗兰克·卡塞尔
Frank Castle,
因与市综合医院枪击案
the gunman wanted in connection with the Metro-General shooting
及最近地狱厨房发生的数十起涉黑人员凶杀案
and linked to dozens of recent gangland-related killings
有关而遭到通缉  现于数小时前
throughout Hell's Kitchen was apprehended just hours ago
在圣麦克公墓外被捕
outside Saint Michael's Cemetery.
一位纽约警方发言人称  今晚
An NYPD spokesman says, "Tonight,
卡塞尔被捕
纽约应向15分局警官
New York has Sergeant Brett Mahoney
布莱特·马霍尼致敬
of the 15th Precinct to thank."
布莱特真厉害
Gotta hand it to Brett.
我很高兴还有他这样的人在守护地狱厨房
I'm glad people like him are looking out for Hell's Kitchen.
是啊
Yeah.
我也很高兴有人在守护他
And I'm glad someone was looking out for him.
媒体称卡塞尔为"冷血变态"
Press are calling Castle "A cold-blooded psychopath."
看来地检官要乐呵呵地
The DA's gonna have a hell of a time
利用对他的诉讼将她打造为一个救世英雄了
using his prosecution to turn herself into a hero.
一切都进展得很顺利
It's all working out perfectly.
-听着让人有点泄气啊  -我...
- Wow, way to bring us down. - I'm...
乔茜  能把电视关上吗
Hey, Josie, would you mind turning the TV off?
有常客嫌烦了
It's upsetting some of the regulars.
我觉得我们今晚已经听够惩罚者的事了
I think we've had enough Punisher for one evening.
-是吧  -好吧  我要为此干一杯
- All right? - Hmm. Okay. I'll drink to that.
敬布莱特以及  安全的地狱厨房
To Brett and... a safe Hell's Kitchen.
干杯
Hear, hear.
-我再去买点酒  -好
- I'm gonna get us another round. - Good.
希望你们俩还能再来点烈的
I hope you two saved room for shots.
-再来份一样的  -不不
- Same again. - Oh, no, no.
一口闷
Oh, shots.
谢了  福吉
Thanks, Fog.
你还好吧
You okay?
挺好的
Yeah.
好吧  听起来没什么说服力
Okay, that wasn't convincing, was it?
我不知道  我只是...
I don't know, I just, uh...
像今天这样的日子...
days like today...
总能让我回想起生活是多么美好
remind me how precious life can be, you know?
你哥哥是什么样的人
What's your brother like?
他很可爱  他...
Uh, he's sweet. He's...
是个好哥哥
a good brother.
小心点  马特
Careful, Matt.
什么意思
What's that?
继续这样下去  你可就要收获你的幸福了
Keep going like this, you just might end up happy.
而对于一个天主教徒来说  这是相当危险的
And for a Catholic boy, that's a pretty dangerous thing.
我不懂你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
祝你成功  马特·默多克
Godspeed, Matt Murdock.
接下来去哪
Hey, where next?
回家
Home.
我要睡上一星期
I'm gonna sleep for a week.
听了某人的馊主意  一口闷了那么多烈酒
Someone had the awful idea of doing shots.
我今晚已经刺激够了
I think I've had enough excitement for one evening.
-明早见  -好的
- See you two in the morning. - Okay. Yeah.
-再见  福吉  -再见
- See ya, Fog. - Bye.
你介意这雨吗
Do you mind the rain?
不
No.
那我陪你走回家
Then I'll walk you home.
乔茜酒吧
-我能邀你共进晚餐吗  -当然
- Can I take you to dinner? - Yes.
-明天  -好
- Tomorrow? - Yes.
晚安  凯伦
Good night, Karen.
晚安  马特
Good night, Matt.
你好  马修
Hello, Matthew.
艾丽卡
Elektra.